Hello Guy Welcome to another video of Stock
Market Friends III Lombard General
Insurance has presented its June quarter
financial results The audited
financial results
of the June quarter are out which we will cover in this video today
Friends let's start the video
and there is
no update from the company regarding dividend so let's go to the
results The numbers are in lax and if we
talk about income then this time the income is
533519 crores Last quarter it was
5153 crores and in the June 23 quarter the
income is 4540 crores Quarter on
quarter year on year The income of both has
increased but the expenses
of the company are Total expense this time is around
48.4 crores Last quarter there was an expense of 46038
crores and in the June 23 quarter there was an
expense of 4209 crores Quarter on
quarter year on year Expenses have also
increased according to the income
after which the operating profit is 50.4  Crore
in the previous quarter of
5615 crore and in the June 23 quarter the
operating profit is 3312 crore, it is
down quarter on quarter and has increased year on
year. What is the reason for the downfall?
Expenses which were incurred very heavily
and this expense
of Guys company has increased. If we see, the
company's expense was other expenses
which was 25.6 crore, which has been much higher than the previous quarter
and due to this the
profit of Guys company has increased and apart from this Guys
outstanding claim which includes
IB NR and IB AR,
this time there has been a change in it, Guys, which can be
seen, outstanding expense was around 686 crore,
its profit was down quarter on
quarter and here the profit of the company
which came out after that was
7739 crore before tax, 697.7 crore in the previous quarter
and in the June 23 quarter there is an
operating profit of 520 crore, quarter on
quarter year on year back  It has been
seen increasing and this has happened
because if you look at the expenses here, it has been added
because this time a
lot of addition has been made to the company, which is the
provision for depreciation in the value of investment, this
time Rs 30.3 crore has been added and this is the reason
guys quarter on quarter profit,
after tax
profit of recovery is Rs 580 crore, in the last quarter it was Rs
51.5 crore and in the June 23 quarter there is a
profit of Rs 39.3 crore, quarter on
quarter and year on year EPS has increased in both
.  The company's result has increased by 68 quarter on
quarter year on year,
which is a very strong
page, very good results have been seen
because not only the income but the profit
of the company has also been seen increasing, it is a
very strong result, the result of the patch
came out to be 455, the company has published the result, if we
talk about the share then 18
86.972610
or in the short term guys there will be a little risk in
entering because it is already
running in the overbought zone, but still guys the
result has been presented very good, so you
can consider it and hold it, if you have already kept the stock then you
can hold it and if you
want to enter then you can enter in the long term,
so we are
ending the video here, if you have any
doubt ask in the comment box, we will meet
in the next video, postpone then bye bye